## LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mattheus

# **Matthew Kehoe**

Trilingual (English, French & Spanish), Senior Renewals specialist with 4 years established experience in client facing roles. Strong analytical and problemsolving skills developed through tech industry experience. My key focus is to provide excellent client experiences built on solid analytics for both internal and external customers.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

#### October 2018 - Current

## **SENIOR RENWALS SPECIALIST &**

## **RENWALS SPECIALIST** – Qualtrics, Ireland

- + Coordinate and co-manage renewal strategy for EMEA region.
- + Design and distribute tailored renewals reports to Sales and Customer Success functions (Salesforce).
- + Process client renewals in compliance with financial policies (Netsuite).
- + Collaborate with AR and renewals functions globally in the review and analysis of KPIs (Tableau).

# Sept 2017 – May 2018

## GRADUATE SKILLS PROGRAMME TUTOR – University of Glasgow, UK

- + Deliver 2-hour workshops on employability and transferable skills.
- + Analyse programme data and provide guidance on marketing strategies.
- + Review and critically evaluate student portfolios.
- + Promote programme at student conferences and promotional events.

## May 2016 – July 2016

# MARKETING INTERN-Pearson Communication, UK

- + Perform market analysis and research on competition.
- + Structure financial plan and pricing proposition for product.
- + Liaise between client Marketing, Design and Administrative departments.
- + Assist in employee attendance data analysis for payroll department.

# June 2017 – August 2017

# WARRANTY ASSESSOR – Accenture Operations, Czech Republic

- + Execute compliance verification and analysis on warranty claims in SAP.
- + Provide guidance and support to client dealerships.
- + Evaluate country performance and report to management in Asia.
- + Identify and design automation tools (VBA) for transactional processes.

## June 2017 – August 2017

## PR TEAM LEAD - Deliveroo, UK

- + Coordinate team of 6 PR agents during Glasgow launch.
- + Source potential candidates and assist in recruitment.
- + Train new employees in job procedure and about organisational culture.
- + Monitor agents to ensure performance complies with company standards.

EDUCATION	
2014 – 2018	<ul> <li>MASTER OF ARTS (MA), BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT – University of Glasgow</li> <li>+ First-class degree (1:1)</li> <li>+ Senior Honors representative for Undergraduate learning and teaching committee</li> <li>+ Class representative for International Marketing Consultancy &amp; Entrepreneurship courses</li> </ul>
2014 – 2018	JUNIOR HONOURS YEAR ABROAD – Université du Québec a Montreal  + Grade A average  + International Ambassador for Study Abroad Programme  + Placed 3rd in PwC Montreal Case competition representing UQAM
AWARDS	
2019 2018 2018	BEST SALES SUPPORT TEAM for Renewals team performance (EOQ) ADAM SMITH SCHOLAR AWARD for academic excellence GLASGOW GOGLOBAL AWARD Multinational projects and international involvement
LANGUAGES	
English French Spanish Czech	NATIVE SPEAKER NATIVE SPEAKER FULL PROFESSIONAL PROFICIENCY BEGINNER
August 2017	GLOBAL LEADERSHIP MINDSET – Aperian  Management training in the use of cross-cultural frameworks  and frame-shifting to leverage multicultural team capabilities  when working in international environments.
February 2016	GLOBAL LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE – Common Purpose  Week-long training programme focusing on developing various leadership styles and soft skills.
March 2015	GRADUATE PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT PROGRAMME – ILM  Three-day long training programme based in an office environment to develop team working skills and how to build on personal strengths.